Guide to the Fidelis Zitterbart Manuscripts, 1868-1915 SC.1967.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ouverture: Victor of Rhe: for Orchestra, December 23, 1876; 1 score (59 p.), flute part (4 p.), oboe part (3 p.), clarinet 1 and 2 in B part (3 p.), horn 1 part (3 p.), horn 2 part (3 p.), trumpet 1 in B part (3 p.), trumpet 2 in B part (3 p.), trombone part (3 p.), timpani and drum part (3 p.), v
  - Ouverture: Victor of Rhe - Parts: Viola, December 23, 1876; 13.
  - Ouverture: Victor of Rhe - Parts: Violoncello, December 23, 1876; 14.
  - Ouverture: Victor of Rhe - Parts: Bass, December 23, 1876; 15.
- Rough Riders: Galop: for Piano, 4 Hands: [in C major], 3 p. of music (Box 85, Folder 3)
  Incomplete. The number "12" pasted on cover; crossed off and replaced in pencil with the number "16." Picture of red eagle pasted on outside cover.